Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I - National War Labor Board - Wage Stabilization Board
  - Sub-Series B. General Subject Files, 1943-1955
    - Jurisdiction, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Jurisdictional Disputes, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Jury Duty, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Labor Maritime Industry, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Labor Market Areas, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Lumber Industry, 1944-1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Maintenance of Membership, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Maintenance of Membership, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Meat Packing Industry, 1945-1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Monthly Reports - National War Labor Board, 3rd - 13th, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Monthly Reports - National War Labor Board, 14th - 19th, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - National Wage Stabilization Board Advisory Committee, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - National Wage Stabilization Board, Basic Documents, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - National Wage Stabilization Board, Terminal Report, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - National War Labor Board - Intra-state Cases, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - National War Labor Board - Jurisdiction, 1943-1945 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - National War Labor Board - Memoranda and Opinions, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - National War Labor Board - Miscellaneous File, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - National War Labor Board - Opinions (Hill), 1945 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - National War Labor Board - Policy (General), 1943 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - National War Labor Board - Rare and Unusual Cases, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - National War Labor Board - Representation, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - National War Labor Board - Termination Program, 1945-1947 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - National War Labor Board - Steel Commission, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - National War Labor Board - War Shipping Panel, 1943-1945 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - New Plants, 1951-1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Commission, 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Commission, Directive Orders, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Non Ferrous Metals Commission, 1943-1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Non Ferrous Metals Industry, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Oil Industry, 1946-1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Coast Longshore, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pension Plans, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases - Region 2, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Price Exempt Industries, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Price Relief, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Productivity, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Professional Engineers, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Racial Discrimination, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Railroad and Airline Wage Board, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Railway Labor, 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Railway Labor, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Rare and Unusual Cases, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Reconversion Wage Policy, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Reduction in Hours, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Research and Statistics, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Research and Statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Regional Board - Decisions, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Regional Board - Organization, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Regional Board - Policy, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Regional Board - Recommendations, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Regional Reports - Wage Stabilization Board (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Reopening Clauses, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Retroactivity, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Rubber Cases, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Salary Stabilization Board - Press Releases, 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Salary Stabilization Board - Regulations, 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Salary Stabilization Board - Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Seniority, 1941-1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Settlement of Grievances-, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Shift Differentials, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Shift Differentials, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Shipbuilding Commission, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Shipbuilding Commission (Atlantic Coast Wage Schedules), 1944 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Speeches, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Steel Cases, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Steel Fact Finding Board, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Strikes - National War Labor Board Releases, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Subcontracting, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Substandard, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Supervisory Differentials, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Supervisory Employees - Union Representation, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Tandem, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Telephone, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Textile Cases, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Tool and Die Industry, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Toy and Doll Manufacturing, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Transfer of Jobs, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Trucking Commission, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Trucking Industry, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Trucking Industry, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Union Recognition and Representation, 1944-1945 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1944-1952 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Vacations - Proration, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Wage Adjustments - Airframe Industry, 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wage Adjustments - Coal Industry, 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Wage Adjustments - Coal Industry, 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wage Adjustments - Local Transit Industry., 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wage Adjustments - Textile Industry., 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Wage Adjustments - Rubber Industry., 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Wage Adjustments - Steel Industry, 1942-1945 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Wage and Fringe Data Listings., 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Wage Brackets., 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Wage Decreases., 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Wage Decreases, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Wage Decreases, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Wage Decreases, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Wage Decreases - Draft of Regulations, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Wage Decreases - Legal Opinions, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Wage Decreases - Manuscripts, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Wage Decreases - Notes, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Wage Information, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Wage Memos, 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Wage Movements Under Controls - (Office of Economic Analysis) Washington, D.C., 1952 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Wage Progression, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wage Stabilization - General Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wage Stabilization - Manual (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wage Stabilization - Regional No. 2 Resolutions, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Wage Stabilization Board - Speeches, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Wage Stabilization Committee, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Wage Stabilization Policy - General, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Wage Stabilization Policy - Reconversion Period, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Wage Stabilization Program (General), 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Wages - Guaranteed Annual Wage, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Wages - War Department, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - West Coast Aircraft Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - West Coast Lumber Commission, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - West Coast Lumber Commission - Directive Orders and Opinions, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - West Coast Lumber Commission - Guide Rates, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series C. Appeals, Minutes and Reports
    - Review and Appeals Committee, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      8/29/52, 9/30/52 - 10/30/52; Division 1 and 2 -Minutes
    - General Wage Stabilization Regulation Bulletin #1-10, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      4/13/51; Pension Benefits, Vacations, etc. and Reports
  - Sub-Series D. Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 25, Folder All)
      1/2/46 - 1/18/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 26, Folder All)
      1/21/46 - 1/31/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 27, Folder All)
      2/4/46 - 2/25/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 28, Folder All)
      2/16/46 - 2/27/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 29, Folder All)
      2/1/46 - 2/19/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1946 (Box 30, Folder All)
      2/20/46 - 2/29/46
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 31, Folder All)
      5/15/51 - 7/27/51
    - Transcripts - Executive Session - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder All)
      8/29/51 - 10/18/52
  - Sub-Series E. Conference Reports of Economic Stabilization Agency - Executive Meeting - National Wage Stabilization Board
    - Conference Reports of Economic Stabilization Agency - Executive Meeting - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 33, Folder All)
      6/21/51 - 7/24/51
    - Conference Reports of Economic Stabilization Agency - Executive Meeting - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 34, Folder All)
      8/1/51 - 9/6/51
    - Conference Reports of Economic Stabilization Agency - Executive Meeting - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 35, Folder All)
      9/12/51 - 10/29/51
    - Conference Reports of Economic Stabilization Agency - Executive Meeting - National Wage Stabilization Board, 1952 (Box 36, Folder All)
      3/13/52 - 10/25/52
  - Sub-Series F. Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memoranda, 1952
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 37, Folder All)
      #801-1500
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 38, Folder All)
      #1501-2500
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 39, Folder All)
      #2501-3400
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 40, Folder All)
      #3401-4200
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 41, Folder All)
      #4201-5400
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 42, Folder All)
      #5401-6800
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 42a, Folder 1)
      no.2-5401 through no. 2-6700
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 43, Folder All)
      #6801-7500
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 44, Folder All)
      #7501-8300
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 45, Folder All)
      #8301-9100
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 46, Folder All)
      #9101-10,500
    - Readers File (Numerical Order) - Memorandums, 1952 (Box 47, Folder All)
      #10,501-20,000
  - Sub-Series G. Miscellaneous Publications, Reports, Instruction Sheets
    - Policy Inquiries, Board Actions, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, Reports, 1941-1952 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series H. Manual of Instructions
    - Manual of Instructions, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Procedure Manual - Administrative Services, Budget and Finances
    - Manual of Instructions, 1951-1952 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Personnel - Miscellaneous and Forms
    - Manual of Instructions, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Resolutions
    - Manual of Instructions (Box 50, Folder 1)
      Manual of Operations - Part 1 - Wage Stabilization Policy; Part 2 - Jurisdiction and Authority; Part 3 - Analysis of Petitions
    - Manual of Instructions (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Manual of Operations - Part 4 - Case Processing Procedures
    - Manual of Instructions (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Manual of Operations - Part 5 - Forms
    - Manual of Instructions (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Table of Contents; Preface
    - Manual of Instructions (Box 50, Folder 5)
      I - Basic Statutes and Regulations; II - Wage Stabilization; III - Disputes; IV - Commissions and Industry Panels; V - Reports
  - Sub-Series I. Releases and Memos, 1942-1953
    - Press Releases, No. 1-101., 1951 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      2/5/51 - 9/1/51
    - Press Releases, No. 101-200., 1951-1952 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      8/31/51 - 3/19/52
    - Press Releases, No. 201-303., 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      3/19/52 - 1/2/53
    - Wage Stabilization Board - Summary of Significant Board Actions., 1943-1945 (Box 51, Folder 4-6)
    - Wage Stabilization Board - Interim Field Instructions., 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Wage Stabilization Board - Termination Report., 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - War Labor Board - Field Memorandum 1 - 45 and Index., 1944 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - War Labor Board - Field Memorandum 46 - 85, 1944-1945 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - War Labor Board - Field Memorandum 86 - 155, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Wage Stabilization Board - Field Memorandums No. 157 -213, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Index of War Labor Board Releases, 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - War Labor Board, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      1/2/46 - 4/19/46; Division of Public Information - Releases No. 1 - 39
    - War Labor Board, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      4/30/46 - 6/28/46; Division of Public Information - Releases No. 40 - 67
    - War Labor Board, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      6/30/46 - 9/27/46; Division of Public Information - Releases No. 68 - 96
    - War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      7/26/43 - 4/25/44; Memorandums and Opinions of the General Counsel's Office
    - National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      5/8/44 - 10/9/44; Memorandum and Opinions of the General Counsel's Office
    - War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      8/20/43 - 12/2/44; Memorandums and Opinions of the General Counsel's Office
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series A. Board of Education (New York City and Others)
    Includes Decisions, Notice of Hearings, Award of Arbitrators, Legal Memorandums, Correspondence, Check Stubs, Notice of Appointment, Form Letters, Agreements, Arbitrators' Notes, Union Exhibits.
    - Bethpage Federation of Teachers, Local 1379, American Federation of Teachers vs. Union Free School District #21, Bethpage, NY, Board of Education, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      1/16/1970; #1330-0756-69 Issues: Arbitrability; Bargaining Units.
    - Board of Cooperative Educational Services (BOCES), Nassau County vs. Central Council of Teachers, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      9/5/1973; #1339-0685-72
    - Half Hollow Hills Teachers Association, Inc. vs. Central School District #5, Huntington and Babylon Board of Education - 1, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
      1/26/74, 1/27/74; #1339-0058-74 (2 cases) Issues: Demotions; Posting; Transfers.
    - Half Hollow Hills Teachers Association, Inc. vs. Central School District #5, Huntington and Babylon Board of Education, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      12/6/1974; #1339- 0059-74 Issue: Elimination of Jobs.
    - Hartford Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of Hartford -, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      4/1/1972; #1239-0161-71 Issue: Assignment of New Jobs.
    - New Rochelle Federation of Teachers, Local 280, American Federation of Teachers, vs. Central School District of New Rochelle, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      7/8/1971; #1339-0121-71 Issues: Management's Rights; Duty to Bargain.
    - New Rochelle Federation of Teachers vs. Central School District of New Rochelle - 1, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      1/3/1972; #1339-0764-71 Issues: Classification of Jobs; Salary Schedules.
    - New Rochelle Federation of Teachers, Local 280, American Federation of Teachers, vs. Central School District of New Rochelle -, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      7/19/1972; #1399-0472-72 Issues: Leaves of Absence; Fringe Benefits.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York -, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      12/18/1963; #L38451 NY-L-327-63 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      4/1/1966; L45482 NY-L-110-65 Issues: Discharge; Notice; Classification of Employees.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      1/11/1967; #L-46815 NY-L-416-65 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside of Classification.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      8/30/1966 #1330-0201-66 Issues: Duty to Bargain; Withdrawal of Existing Benefits.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      9/2/1966; #1330-0248-66 Issue: Assignment of New Jobs.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      1/13/1967; #1330-0270-66 Issues: Contractual Duties; Equipment and Physical Facilities.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      2/8/1967; #1330-0401-66 Issues: Compensatory Time Off; Discrimination
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      7/12/68; #1330-0881-66 Issues: Grievances; Grievance Procedure; Medical Release.
    - Attendance Teachers Chapter, United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      3/34/67; #1330-0695-66 Issues: Withdrawal of Existing Benefits; Duty to Bargain.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      4/24/1968; #1330-0276-67 Postponed.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      3/7/1969; #1330-0395-67 Issues: Insurance; Compensation.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      9/27/1968; #1330-0130-68 Issue: Transfers.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      10/10/1968; #1330-0173-68 Withdrawn.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2 vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      10/23/1968; #1330-0174-68 Issue: Posting.
    - Ira Wells vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      6/7/68; #1330-0280-68 Issues: Promotions; Bargaining Units
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      6/21/1968; #1330-0396-68 Issues: Contract Interpretation; Definitions.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      2/18/1969; #1330-0430-68 Issues: Contractual Duties; Transfers.
    - Associated Teachers of Huntington vs. Board of Education, Union Free School District #3, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      8/26//68; #1330-0532-68 Issue: Leaves of Absence.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      1/2/1969; #1330-0757-68 Issues: Grievances; Grievance Procedures.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      1/26/1970; #1330-0682-68 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      2/26/1969; #1330-0686-68 Issue: Notice.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      8/13/1969; #1330-0190-69 Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      3/24/1969; #1330-0194-69 Settled.
    - Morris Grumet, et. al. vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      1/9/1970; #1330-0333-69 Issues: Compensation; Part Time Employees.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      3/6/1970; #1330-0522-69 Issues: Grievances; Grievance Procedure; Files.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      8/3/1970; #1330-0851-69 Issues: Incentive Systems; Incentive Pay.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      1/19/1971; #1330-1112-69 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside of Classification.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      7/31/1970; #1330-0232-71 Issue: Vacancies.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York -, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      4/29/1971; #1339-0339-70 Issues: Hours; Assignment of New Jobs.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      5/27/1971; #1339-0767-70 Issues: Application for Employment; Seniority.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      1/31/1972; #1339-1109-70 Issue: Files.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      3/19/1971; #1339-0326-70 Issue: Retention Rights.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      12/16/1971; #1339-0123-71 Issue: Salary Schedules.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      9/28/1971; #1339-0148-71 Issues: Medical Release; Leaves of Absence.
    - Leslie Lubin vs. Board of Education of City of New York, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      11/8/1971; #1339-0209-71 Issues: Arbitrability; Employees' Rights.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      6/16/1971; #1339-0322-71 No Decision - Transferred to Another Arbitrator.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      6/1/1973; #1339-0371-71 Issue: Severance Pay.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      2/25/1972; #1339-0819-71 Issues: Assignment of Jobs; Workweek.
    - Major Davis vs. Board of Education of City of New York, Community School District #23, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      2/3/1972; #1339-1136-71 No Decision - Withdrawn 2/3/72.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      5/1/1972; #1339-0147-72 No Decision - Withdrawn 5/1/72.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      6/19/1972; #1339-0520-72 No Decision - Withdrawn 5/29/73.
    - United Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of the City of New York, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      10/27/1972; #1339-0163-72 and #1339-0175-72 Award Not Present. Issue: Files.
    - Council of Supervisors and Administrators vs. Board of Education of City of New York, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      3/27/1973; #1339-0892-72 Issue: Vacancies and Hiring.
    - United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, American Federation of Teachers vs. Board of Education of City of New York, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      10/22/1973; #1339- 1121-72 Issues: Grievances; Grievance Procedure.